



Professional Summary

I am IT specialist with more then 15 years of experience in software development. I am hardworking, team and goal oriented, challenge seeking, and work well under pressure.

- Hardware Builds

- System Audits

- Stuff Management

- Information Security

- Hardware maintenance

My experience includes:

- Project Management

- Network Design/Deployment/Administration/Maintenance

- System Administration

- LAN/WAN/Wireless

- Backup/Recovery Plans

- Network Security

- Microfinance software

- Programming with Object Oriented programs, such as Visual Basic 6.0 (2003 started with .NET)

- Client/Server application development and design using Visual Basic 6.0

- Database design, implementation, administration and maintenance using the Microsoft SQL Server

- Microsoft Certified Solutions Developer

- Microsoft Certified System Administrator

Technical Skills

- Hardware/OS: Windows, Windows servers

- Software: MS Visual Basic 6.0/NET, Transact SQL, MSVBA, HTML

Databases: MS SQL Server, MS Access, IBM DB2
Networking: Microsoft Network with Windows Servers

Professional Experience

IT Manager for MicroFinS - Microfinance Organization, with UNHCR as one of Donors (2002-Present)

My role is to project information system, administer and maintain several databases, develop several applications (for salaries, bookkeeping, human resources), provide assistance in the creation of various reports, hardware and network project, design and maintenance, troubleshooting and installation. (System and database Engineer/Administrator & Programmer). I was involved in two MFI software suites:

- <u>Kredits</u> (on MS access and later MS SQL Server databases; installation, administration, maintenance; building custom modules; making custom reports)
- <u>ASPEKT microfinance software</u> (web aplication on MS SQL Server database; analizing bussiness processes, making demands for software development, data migration, installation, administration, maintenance; making custom reports)

I also develop Web sites at www.microfins-dbs.co.rs.

Used: Visual Basic 6.0 for sofware development, MS SQL Server 2015 and MS Access for database design, MS Excell for reports. Network: Windows 2008/2012 Servers, Windows XP/7 workstations, wireles and local area network, Internet.

Reference: Braco Saša Dimitrovski, CEO (<u>bracods@microfins.org.rs</u>)

NIT Solutions (2005-present)

As a associate. Projecting and implementing of network environment, programming several applications (Expense tracking system, System for production, warehouse, invoicing, buying analysis and sales)

Used: Visual Basic 6.0 for sofware development, MS Access for database design, MS Excell for reports.

Network: Windows 2008 Servers, Windows XP/Vista/7 workstations, wireles and local area network, Internet.

Reference: Zoran Novaković, Director (hans@nit-solutions.net)

Donautrade (2001-present)

As a associate. Projecting and implementing of network, hardware and software environment. Programming several applications (Warehouse, Bookkeeping, Invoicing).

Used: Visual Basic 6.0 for sofware development, MS Access for database design, MS Excell for reports.

Network: Windows 2008/2012 Servers, Windows XP/7 workstations, wireles and local area network, Internet.

I also develop Web sites at www.donau.rs, www.donautrade.rs, www.svezakamine.rs.

Reference: Radovan Ranđić, Director (office@donau.rs)

NTE Engineering Beograd (2001-2002)

Participation in developing several two- and three-tier client/server applications. The applications were for the system of parking lots, ticket counter, cash desk.

Used: Visual Basic 6.0 for sofware development, MS SQL Server 2000 for database design.

Reference: Srđan Vuković, Director (srvukovic@sezampro.rs)

Application Software Partner (2001)

Involved in the programming, analysis and design of three-tier client/server application as a associate. The application is for stock market.

Used: Transact SQL for writing Stored Procedures, MS SQL Server 2000 for database design.

Reference: Zvonko Milosavljević, Director (asp@eunet.rs)

AD Jugopetrol Kotor (1996-2001)

Participation in a team whose job was to create an informative center for that company. Our job was to install, test end edit software, project, design and prepair the network and hardware and make web site and intranet, of course maintance also.

We worked on the programming language »IAF«, that was generated from C++ and have a syntax like VBA and some other programming languages, like Visual Basic, FoxPro, MS Access, Transact SQL. Our job was also to project, create and maintain databases on the SQL Server 2000.

Reference: Vasko Petrović, Director of IT sector (vasko.petrovic@jugopetrol.me)

(1996-Present)

I also developed aplications for a number of Clients in Visual Basic on MS Access databases:

- Pamex, Bostek

Reference: Slobodan, Director (office@pamex.me)

- Cigre

Reference: Julija Spajić, Director (office@cigresrbija.rs)

- Farman

Reference: Damir Mandić, Director (damirm@me)

- Dom Zdravlja Kotor

Reference: Mira Pavićević, Accountant (<u>bagzi7@yahoo.com</u>)

CiclodroN

Reference: Aleksandar Bogojević, Director (ciclodrom@hotmail.com)

- SpajicCo

Reference: Darko Spajić, Director (spajicco@eunet.rs)

- Krypton

Reference: Dejan Vasiljević, Director (office@krypton.co.rs)

- Etno Salon

Reference: Nemanja Ranđić, Director (randja@gmail.com)

...

Education:

1991-1996 »Higher Business School«, at the Informatic department (in title of Informatic Engineer) in Belgrade, Serbia.

2006-2008 <u>»The Faculty of Business Information Science«</u>, at the Projecting and Programming of the Information Systems department (in title of Dipl. Engineer for Projecting and Programming of the Information Systems) in Belgrade, Serbia.

Courses undertaken

September 2001 Microsoft Certified Solutions Developer (Visual Basic 6.0, SQL Server 2000) December 2003 Microsoft Certified System Administrator (Windows 2003 Server, Windows XP)

Biography:

Date of birth: April 9, 1972Place of birth: Kotor, Montenegro

- Address: Kornelija Stankovica 4, Belgrade

- Country: Serbia

Phone: 0038111-308-86-48
Mobile: 0038164-18-36-034
E-mail: nijepa@gmail.com

- Languages: English